<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on CCTMC</title>
    <link>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on CCTMC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 14:03:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maninwindow.github.io/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CCTMC Party</title>
      <link>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/officers_party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:42:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/officers_party/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is another special day for CCTMCers. We spent whole day parting together. Almost everyone shared their favorite dishes in sense of a home party. Additionally, it turned out a great chance to discover talents in our family as well. Raunak is a great guitarist and vocalist, almost everyone is great singer and gamer.
Following are our shots of memorable moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dance at the Dalian Conference</title>
      <link>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/dalian_conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 19:00:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/dalian_conference/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Toastmasters annual conference is a special event that brings members together around Chine. Beatiful city Dalian was where we celebrate this unique event of 2019.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;CCTMCers brought diversity to this event. Beautiful ladies from our club dressed up differently on this day. Audiences were captivated by elegancy and beauty of their dance.
Beautiful memories Here we are to enjoy some beautiful pictures from the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Spring Outing</title>
      <link>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/spring_outing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 14:06:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maninwindow.github.io/events/spring_outing/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Last Saturday, CCTMCers went outing at the Olympic Forest Park. We had a great time burning calories and taking snapshots despite the cold and mizzly weather
Warm up session &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Participants were devided into three teams: Red, Blue and Yellow. Let&amp;rsquo;s do some warming-up together!
 
 
 
 
Walking race session Rules of the Game &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1. Both roaming and jogging are ok; each team&amp;rsquo;s result is based on the last-arriving member&amp;rsquo;s record;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>